[Music]
imagine winning this Lambo by just being
good at what you're good at that's
exactly what I did my Lambo will be won
by one of these eight lucky people and
the way the winner would be chosen as
crazy as this sounds is by playing rock
paper scissors literally rock paper
scissors for to win my Lamborghini one
of these eight people are going to win
it but before we know who the winner is
of winning my quarter million dollar
Lamborghini let's see the story of how
this originally started let's go and it
all started on April 4th where I said in
this reel 21 000 comments 21 000 likes
is all you guys have to do to win my
Lamborghini yes get the title to my
Lamborghini so yeah we hit the 21 000
likes and I am a man of my word and I
keep it to the end so since we hit the
21 000 likes we started the trading
competition and they all happen here we
rented out this 20 000 square foot
hanger to organize the event where we
rock paper scissors to see who's gonna
win the lump so we had the boy our
Atlanta come out and paint the car live
he did a one-on-one Roars Royce Orange
splatter all over it we had participants
from the lambo giveaway that came from
all around the world to do the rock
paper scissors we had Traders that
everybody that came they signed my drip
car you guys are just there in the video
what they signed on my gift card we had
the 21 pillar Challenge and then Sensei
my boy my brother surprised me with a
brand new AP that I did not expect and
most importantly connected with the
entire community
so before continuing I'm going to show
you a clip of me explaining how you can
win this Lamborghini on one of my other
videos about a month or two ago so if
you haven't subscribed hit that
subscribe button because you might miss
out on winning another Lamborghini you
know how rocket has a two-step
evaluation to get funded by the way
they're adding a one-step challenge soon
but that's completely off topic they
have a two evaluation process to get
funded
so there's going to be a two evaluation
process to win the lambo giveaway so in
the second phase of evaluation there's
going to be 10 people selected to win
the lambo how do you become part of
these 10 people very simple the first
way is you register for the free
competition on their website it is
literally free you you just sign up you
get credentials and if you end up in the
top five of the leaderboard at the end
of the competition you move on to the
second stage it is completely for free
every single day you can go and you can
see the stats of where you are if you're
top 10 top 15 top 20 or if you're in the
top five so you know to maintain so at
the end of the competition if you are in
the top five you automatically move to
the second phase of the giveaway if you
don't end up in the top five you still
have a chance how so if you buy a rocket
21 challenge during the whole entire
month uh that the competition is going
on and at the end of the competition
you're not in the top five we will be
selecting five people at random from
anybody that purchases a rocket 21
challenge then those five people that we
select around and we'll do it live on
our YouTube or Instagram live they move
on to the second part along with the
five people from the competition so from
the 10 total participants only six were
able to make it to the event because
four were out of the US and they just
able to travel to come to Miami so they
got compensated otherwise but for the
six that came we had Hassan kendri we
had two hectares we had anabin and
Johnny
[Music]
oh this is to throw paint on it
we're gonna literally throw paint on
this phone right now never been done
before
everybody
two three High sides 244 so these guys
are about three four hours early to the
event
s
exactly man I was just the FIU event
never again bro I'm gonna come to
Florida bro I was in that line for hours
and I wasn't even close to getting in
yeah so I was like you know I gotta come
I mean you know I just took my
graduation shoes you know 20 minutes
away and then I pulled up here oh yeah I
just came here for us so you know no
excuses man I got my book I'm ready bro
all right
yeah dude this is what it's all about
bro I want you guys
all right so I set him up with food for
being here three hours thank you bro
all right enjoy it don't go crazy
get a drift car they said it would be
fun they said
[Music]
I swear I have no idea
just come on up
all right perfect so now I'm gonna let
these three contestants since we started
first we're gonna pull out a name
whatever name they put out they're going
to go against that person
Kendrick Rodriguez
[Music]
foreign
yeah
so it's very clear Construction
[Applause]
Paper Scissors Shoot
oh
[Applause]
by the way if you guys don't know the
sign made this stage by an air literally
by her hair you remember that right
yeah
all right let's do it you guys are ready
all right so we got three two
okay
[Music]
rock paper scissors
foreign
we now have Johnny and evil and Hector
left so basically what we're going to do
is from inside this jar we're going to
get their names and then I'm just going
to select one name whatever name I
select or somebody random select gets
instantly eliminated and we have the two
final contestants to rock paper scissors
so it's fair
oh yeah
all right here it is so shake it shake
it shake it shake it shake it and
whatever name you select automatically
gets removed
it's crazy I don't know if you guys know
who Mr Beast is
okay all right so whatever name you
select you're gonna You're Gonna Save
[Music]
um
so now we have our final two contestants
which is the journeyman
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
it was at this moment he knew he
up I have to apologize
[Applause]
[Music]
come on
[Applause]
[Music]
that's all I can say
foreign
[Music]
ER so it is the next day and we're about
to
hand this guy the lambo keys because
last night he couldn't take it because
he couldn't figure out how to put
insurance just for like legality purpose
and like Risk purposes I didn't let him
drive off in the car until he had his
own insurance on it so we're about to
get him the car so he takes off
oh look at that they're already opening
up the game
still I still can't believe I'm giving
this guy a smart I just can't believe it
here they've been here since like seven
in the morning
all right so everything was fake bro I'm
kidding they ask you how you are you
just have to say that you're fine when
you're not really fine but you just
can't get into it because they would
never understand
so I'm with the official winner of the
Lamborghini so bro I have a couple of
questions right
um how does it feel to drive from
Wilmington you brought his parents all
the way down like a 60-hour drive how
does it feel to be the one the only one
in the competition that wanted to keep
it on for everybody else that was in the
rock paper scissors they wanted to sell
their car and get rid of it so how does
it feel how does everything feel so
wrong I don't feel like amazing I don't
really have to work for describe how how
I really feel but I want to appreciate
you
of course
and I wanna I wanna have fun with this
Maybe
if you wanted to take the rap off I'm
like bro leave the rap on but you can
have it so you're gonna leave the rap on
everything yeah
yeah enjoy it bro I hope you have a lot
of fun with it bro
[Music]
this guy's crazy
just like that it's a wrap we got the
drip car tow truck heading home now
we're down one car so now that only
means one thing
time so this is the aftermath of how
many people sign my drift car look
whoever did this uh you already know
what you did here buddy it didn't come
out that nice but I told the staff and
in terms of the only sign the quarter
panel people signed everywhere so I mean
but this is really what it's all about
like giving back to the community and
just engaging with the people because
every single one of these guys that you
know basically signed the car they're
pretty much with me like essentially
like take them to my home but if you
want to be like me or any of these
people to make anywhere from a thousand
to a thousand five hundred a week from
Trading just click the link in the
description below there's a free video
there is a webinar that I think is going
to help you guys to be motivated and
then learn because if I would have seen
that same video that I have for you guys
in the link in the description below it
would have easily made me a thousand to
a thousand five hundred a week much
sooner than it did so thank you guys for
watching the video to the end and I'll
see you guys in the next video